// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A ___ is normalized after it has been organized",
    answer: "Database",
    options: [
      "Table.",
      "Row  ",
      "Database",
      "Column"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "By normalizing relations or sets of relations, one minimizes ___.",
    answer: "Redundancy",
    options: [
      "Data",
      "Redundancy",
      "Fiels ",
      "Dataase"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " In addition to removing undesirable characteristics, normalization also eliminates ___ anomalies",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Insert",
      "Update ",
      "Delete",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " In practical applications, how many types of Normal Forms are there?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "BCNF"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " When a relation contains an atomic value, it is a ___ relation." ,
    answer: "1NF",
    options: [
      "1NF",
      "2NF",
      "3NF",
      "BCNF",
  
      
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "2NF relations are those that are in 1NF with all the attribute types dependent on the ___ key." ,
    answer: "Primary",
    options: [
      "Primary ",
      "Super",
      "Foreign",
      "Composite"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "  When a relation is in 2NF and there is ___, it is in 3NF." ,
    answer: "No Transition Dependency",
    options: [
      "Transition Dependency",
      "No Transition Dependency",
      "Relational Dependency",
      "No Relational Dependancy"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " A relation is in ___ if it is in Boyce Codd normal form and does not have any multivalued dependencies." ,
    answer: "4NF",
    options: [
      "3NF",
    "4NF",
      "5NF",
      " 1NF"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A relation is in ___ if it is in Boyce Codd normal form and does not have any multivalued dependencies." ,
    answer: "Lossless",
    options: [
      "Lossless",
      "Losser",
      "Lossful",
      "Full"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "  What is TRUE about the Second Normal Form (2NF)?" ,
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "	Relational must belong to 1NF in the 2NF",
      "All attributes other than the primary key are fully functional in the second normal form",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
];